connectnigeria.com 2014-06-25

# connectnigeria.com - Privacy Policy

What information do we collect at Connect Nigeria?   

Connect Nigeria collects information from you when you register, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form on the website.   
When ordering or registering on Connect Nigeria, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.  

### What do we use your information for?   

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional news about Connect Nigeria, updates, related product or service information etc. 

### How do we protect your information?   

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.  
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?   

###  Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  

###  Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  

###  Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.connectnigeria.com/terms_and_conditions.php  

###  Your Consent 

By using our Connect Nigeria, you consent to our online privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.   
This policy was last modified on December 5, 2013

### Contacting Us   

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   

www.connectnigeria.com/contact.php  
26A, Awori Road, Off Corporation Drive, Dolphin Estate  
Ikoyi, Lagos  
Nigeria  
(0809) 800-5000
